人人影视
YYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
大家今天怎么样  有什么让你们生气的事儿吗
How's everybody doing today? Any anger problems?
今早我把一个停车表女管理员给骂了
Actually, I screamed at a meter maid this morning.
翻译： 重案组李Sir  青椒  胖达
-给了你多少钱的罚单  -我没接到罚单
- How bad was the ticket? - Oh, I didn't get a ticket,
但是我以前接到很多
but I've just gotten so many in the past,
翻译： 胖兔纯  Hannah小颂颂  安sim
我觉得她是自找的
I felt she had it coming.
看到了吗  就是这个
See? See? Right there.
时间轴： 魔人jo
我觉得这就是你们都面临的问题
That is exactly one of the problems I think you all face.
在事情并没有真的发生之前
Getting angry when you assume something bad
校对： holyzch
你们就都往坏处想
is going to happen before it ever does.
所以我就想出了一个小游戏
So I have come up with a little game
总监&后期： 孤帆
来帮助你们解决这个问题
to help you deal with this issue head-on.
喝酒
Oh, getting drunk.
我七岁的时候就玩儿这个游戏了
I've been playing this game since I was seven.
不不  不是喝酒
No, no, no, no. We're not getting drunk.
有点像是用啤酒罐子玩的俄罗斯轮盘
It's kind of like Russian roulette with beer cans.
我叫它"啤酒猎人"
Or what I like to call "The Beer Hunter."
先别管我们喝不喝  你就非买国产货吗
Whether we drink it or not, did you have to go domestic?
我刚把其中一罐啤酒给摇了
Now, I just shook up one of these beers,
但是我忘记是哪一罐了
but I don't know which one.
你们都要把啤酒拿到下巴处  然后打开
So you're all going to hold the beer up to your chin and open it.
就会有人湿身了
So somebody's gonna get soaked.
这里有六罐啤酒我只摇了一罐
I don't know. There's six beers and I only shook up one.
可能没人会湿身
Maybe nobody will get soaked.
从你开始吧  诺兰
Let's start with you, Nolan.
你怎么一点都不紧张
You weren't nervous at all.
我看过很多电影  第一个都不会中
I've seen enough movies. It's never the first one.
好了  蕾西  你是下一个
All right, Lacey, you're next.
气死我了
I'm so pissed right now.
我刚弄完头发  要是弄得我全身都是
I just got my hair done. If this gets all over me--
就会是你另一个平常的周六而已
It'll be just another one of your Saturday nights.
看吧  蕾西  还什么事都没发生呢  你就生气了
You see, Lacey? You're getting angry and nothing's happened yet.
而且  可能什么都不会发生
And odds are, nothing will.
但是我们知道不会是诺兰
But we know it's not Nolan
只剩下四个人和六罐啤酒
and there's only four of us and six beers cans.
就是说有百分之五十的几率会是我
That means there's a 50% chance it's me.
百分之百的几率我以后不会让你帮我做账了
And there's a 100% chance I'll never ask you to do my taxes.
谢谢你给我上的课  查理
Hmm. Thank you for the lesson, Charlie,
但是你们都错过了好戏  因为我湿身的时候超美的
but you all missed out because I look amazing when I'm wet.
帕特里克  把你的啤酒给她
Patrick, give her your beer.
不不  艾德是下一个
No, no, no. No, no. Ed's next.
我的没事
Mine's fine.
天呐  那就是我了
Oh, my God, then it's me.
该死的  再给我一罐
Damn it. Give me another one.
不不  抱歉  游戏结束了
No, no. Sorry. Game's over.
我知道你的把戏
I know what you did.
你一罐都没摇
You didn't shake any of them up.
不  事实上  我摇了四罐
No, actually, I shook up, like, four of them.
我不知道到底是怎么回事
I don't know what the hell happened.
好吧  如果我们大家都完事儿了  蕾西也不会湿身
All right, if we're all done and Lacey's not gonna get wet,
那我来宣布点事
I have some surprising news.
你们还记得上礼拜我得到的那份开车的工作吗
You remember that job I got last week driving the limo?
还没被开除呢
I still have it.
-太棒了  诺兰  -是啊
- That's great, Nolan. - Yeah.
我邀请大家坐我的豪华礼车兜兜风
I'm inviting everybody out for a free limo ride.
我们就能面对面坐着聊天了
So we can sit across from each other and talk.
太激动了
How exciting.
事实上  我有个超棒的客人给了我一百美元的小费
Actually, I have an awesome client who gives me $100 tips,
我带你们去马里布吃午餐
so I'm taking you all out to lunch in Malibu
这是一个很好地团队协作训练
That sounds like a great team-building exercise.
我听说有家新的塔可钟和冰雪皇后店
And I hear the new Malibu Taco Bell/Dairy Queen
就建在水上
is right on the water.
谢谢你破坏惊喜
Thanks for giving it away.
我去  我从不拒绝免费午餐
I'm in. I never turn down a free lunch.
或者是家装中心前面的
Or one of those bags of top
那几袋子上层土一样
soil in front of a home improvement center.
艾德  那些袋子不是免费的
Ed, those bags are not free.
放到门前了就是谁抢到算谁的
Anything out front is fair game.
这个国家欠我的
This country owes me.
抱歉打扰了
Whoops. Sorry to interrupt.
-没关系  -很好
- No problem. - Mm. Very nice.
你们知道我放在我家门口的
Oh, you know the garden
花园浇水管吗
hose that I leave out in front of my house?
-不见了  -也许你不该放在门前
- It's missing. - Maybe you shouldn't leave it out front.
好吧
Okay.
好了  大家  手指交叉[祈祷]
Okay, everybody, cross your fingers.
-为什么  -快点
- Why? - Just do it.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
感谢上帝  居然成功了一罐
Thank God one of them worked.
我还以为今天倒霉到家了呢
I thought today was gonna suck.
大家好  我来介绍一下小组的新成员
Hi, everyone. I'd like to introduce a new member of our group.
-兰迪·沃伦  -是兰迪·沃伦医生
- Randy Warren. - Uh, Dr. Randy Warren.
不  心理协会已经取消了你的头衔
Actually, the APA revoked that title
因为你骗了很多人
because you were a fraud.
可是已经把我的真名改成了兰迪·沃伦医生
Well, the jokes on you because I had my name
所以你活该丢人现眼吧
legally changed to Dr. Randy Warren.
我妈妈一定会很自豪
Ooh, my mama gonna be so proud
她儿子要嫁给一位医生了
when I tell her I'm marrying a doctor.
这只是时间问题  亲爱的
Oh, it's just a matter of time, sugar.
你这位亲爱的心理咨询师
Look, you should know your beloved therapist
告发了我  还把我送去了监狱
turned me in and got me sent to prison.
我只是害你被吊销执照而已
I got your license revoked
因为你声称有灵媒能力
because you claimed to have psychic powers.
是你自己绑架了心理协会的董事
And you're the one who kidnapped an APA board member.
开车去了墨西哥  车里还全是迷幻药
And drove to Mexico with 100 tabs of LSD
车还是偷来的警车
in a stolen police car.
可是第一张多米诺骨牌是你推倒的
But you knocked over the first domino.
查理  关于兰迪医生你说错一件事
Charlie, you're wrong about Dr. Randy.
他确实有魔法
He has magical powers.
我们还没说话
Before we ever talked,
他就知道我参加了什么黑帮
he knew the name of the gang I was in.
你脖子上写了
It's written on your neck.
可他是倒着读出来的
Yeah, but he read it upside down
因为我把他倒吊在了栏杆边上
while I was holding him over the railing.
-查理  能跟你聊聊吗  -我正在做诊疗
- Charlie, can I talk to you? - I'm in the middle of group.
就是这事  典狱长要取消这个活动
It's about the group. The warden is shutting it down.
-天啦噜  -什么
- Ooh! - What?
如果你想把名字改成
If you want to change your
"失业的心理咨询师查理·古德森"
name to "Unemployed Therapist Charlie Goodson,"
我可以帮忙
I have some extra forms.
算了吧
I'm good.
真遗憾  我们没来得及聊聊
You know, it's a shame we never got a chance to talk about
你为什么那么讨厌黑人和墨西哥人
why you hate black people and Mexicans so much.
愤怒管理
第二季第六十九集
我做集体诊疗做了四年
I've put in four hard years with that group.
那些人恢复了不少
And those men are doing great.
为什么典狱长会不满意呢
Why would the warden be against anger therapy?
不知道  发来邮件说要取消了
I don't know. The email just says they're shutting it down.
你的金属餐叉实验也得结束了
Oh, and your metal fork experiment is over.
与餐叉有关的刺伤事件很难以承受
Even one fork-related stabbing is too many.
金属餐叉的事情无所谓  但是
You know, they can have the metal forks, but screw him.
-我的小组诊疗不能取消  -查理  等等
- I'm not letting him take away my group. - Charlie, wait.
你要是惹毛了典狱长  诊所也会有危险
If you piss off the warden, we could lose the clinic, too.
来使用一点愤怒管理的技巧吧
Let's use some anger management techniques.
深呼吸几次
Take a few deep breaths.
好点了吗
Better?
不  我现在不仅暴怒  而且头晕
No. Now I'm furious and lightheaded.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
来做点蠢事
Let's try something silly
降低一下逐渐上升的愤怒指数
to break the escalating pattern of angry thoughts.
-比如  -我不知道
- Like what? - I-- I don't know.
-拿走了你的鼻子  -不好玩  还给我
- Got your nose. - That's not funny. Give it back.
还给我
Give it back!
好吧
Okay.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
以前去家庭野餐
I had a drunk uncle who took my nose
我叔叔喝醉了  拿走了我的鼻子
when I was five at a family picnic.
结果在踢足球的时候心脏病发死了
He had a heart attack playing softball
没有把鼻子还给我
and never gave it back.
这是我二年级同学蒂米·威尔逊的鼻子
I stole this one off Timmy Wilson in second grade,
所以不喜欢别人碰
so it's a bit of a sore spot.
诺兰  你让艾德坐下行吗
Nolan, can you tell Ed to please sit down?
我只是让附近的女士们
Hey, I'm just giving the neighborhood ladies
饱饱眼福
a little something to enjoy.
她们确实很享受
Oh, they're enjoying it.
卡罗  你看  好像是一只特殊的海象
Carol, look. That must be a special walrus.
还用大型豪华轿车送去动物园呢
They're driving him to the zoo in a limousine.
我是诺兰
You're rolling with Nolan.
威廉斯先生您好
Oh, hey, Mr. Williams.
当然可以  我就在附近
Sure, I can. I'm in the neighborhood right now.
马上就过去
I'll be over in a sec.
抱歉
Sorry, guys.
你们得下车了  我要去接客人
You're all gonna have to get out so I can pick up a client.
下车  这里可是荒郊野地
Get out? We're in the middle of nowhere.
这里是贝弗利山庄  你从小住这里
We're in Beverly Hills. You grew up here.
我知道  但我不能别别人看见和他们混一起
I know, but I can't be seen with these guys.
就是因为车窗不透明
I mean, the only reason
我才过来的
I'm here is because the windows are tinted.
抱歉  但我的顾客
I'm sorry, but my customer
不希望车里有其他人  他小费也给得多
expects the car to himself and he tips me big.
放松点  诺兰
Lighten up, Nolan.
你就说我们是洛杉矶豪车巡查委员会的
Just tell him that we're the LA Limo Inspection Committee.
我们的工作就是在车上坐一天
And we're just here to sit in for the day
-给你的服务质量把关  -那我干得如何
- and make sure you're doing a good job. - How am I doing?
我们不能向外透露
We're not at liberty to disclose
此次报告的内容
what is in our report at this time.
那好吧
All right, fine.
我马上回来
I'll be right back. Be cool.
他没拔车钥匙  我们去拉斯维加斯吧
He left the keys in the ignition. Let's go to Vegas.
拉斯维加斯就是个臭水沟
Ah, hell. Vegas is a cesspool.
我们去卢博克[得克萨斯州城市]吧
Let's go to Lubbock.
等等  那家伙挺帅的
Wait. That guy's really cute.
等等  诺兰  这是搞错了吗
Uh, excuse me, Nolan. Is there some sort of mix up here?
我应该早点告诉你的
Oh, I probably should have told you, but today,
今天洛杉矶豪车巡查委员会
I'm being observed by
会莅临监督我的工作
the Los Angeles Limo Inspection Committee.
希望你能接受
Hope that's okay.
我们巡查豪车  给你非凡的乘坐体验
We've inspected the limo and the ride is smooth.
就像刚热蜡去毛一般的丝滑
Like just-got-waxed smooth.
我是奎恩
I'm Quinn.
我的身体就像体操运动员一样灵活
I'm flexible like a gymnast.
宅子不错
Nice mansion.
还行吧  这是西海岸的
It's okay... for the West Coast.
我在马沙文雅岛的别墅更棒
My house on Martha's Vineyard is much nicer.
那我就开门见山地问你吧
So I'm just gonna ask you outright,
你有没有可能是同性恋
is there any chance that you're gay?
不  完全不是
No. Not at all.
你的语气里好像有些许犹豫
I heard a little hesitation.
明晚八点你有什么安排吗
So what are you doing around 8:00 tomorrow night?
可能会在做完裸体瑜伽后
Probably soaking in a bubble bath
泡一个泡泡浴
after naked yoga
并渴望有一个人来按摩我酸痛的身体
wishing someone was there to massage my aching muscles.
干吗这么问
Why?
诺兰  你明天能载我们去约会吗
Nolan, you can drive us on a date tomorrow night, can't you?
当然  没问题
Yeah, sure. That's fine.
能等我一下吗
Can you excuse me for a minute?
喂  是我  诺兰
Hello. Yes, Nolan.
没错  我确实想跟他去约会
Yes, I really do want to go out with him.
刚刚检查了一下胎压
Just checking the tire pressure.
我们可以出发了
We're good to go.
我要见麦克拉斯基典狱长
I need to see Warden Maclasky.
抱歉  典狱长不在
I'm sorry, the warden's no longer here.
三点四十五就下班了吗
At a quarter to 4:00?
他真是兢兢业业呀啊
Well, I certainly applaud his commitment to his work.
他会回来吗
Is he coming back?
周二他被金属叉子捅了之后就辞职了
No, he quit on Tuesday after being stabbed with a metal fork.
还有什么能帮你的吗
Is there something I can help you with?
那我要见新的典狱长
Yeah, I guess I need to see the new warden.
-请问你的名字  -查理·谷德森
- And who shall I say is here? - Charlie Goodson.
让他给我解释清楚
And tell him he better be prepared to explain
为什么终止我的监狱治疗组
why he's shutting down my prison group.
哈特利典狱长  查理·谷德森来了
Warden Hartley, Charlie Goodson is here to see you.
先提醒你  我待会儿会骂一些脏话
Just so you know, I am about to use some language,
就算你在最高戒备的监狱里工作
which, even though you work in a maximum security prison,
也可能没听过这么粗俗的语言
you may not have heard before.
-我是哈特利典狱长  -你好  我是查理·谷德森
- I'm Warden Hartley. - Hey. How are you? Charlie Goodson.
很荣幸见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
请原谅我的用词
Sorry you had to hear that.
我下班了
Well, I'm off.
周末愉快
Have a great weekend.
好的  等等
Yup. Wait.
你见到麦克拉斯基典狱长了吗
Uh, what happened with Warden Maclasky?
他恢复监狱治疗小组了吗
Did he reinstate the prison group?
对了  麦克拉斯基典狱长走了
Oh, yeah. Warden Maclasky is gone,
但我和哈特利典狱长说了
but I did speak to Warden Hartley.
然后哈特利典狱长会考虑一下的
And Warden Hartley is willing to think about it.
我要和哈特利典狱长一起共进晚餐
In fact, I'm taking Warden Hartley to dinner
来讨论治疗小组的更多细节问题
to discuss the group in greater detail.
-周一见  -你为什么用这种语调
- See you Monday. - Why are you talking like that?
我的声音就这样啊  乔丹
This is my voice, Jordan.
为什么你的语调听着像卡通片里的花栗鼠
Why do you talk like a cartoon chipmunk?
不不  你故意不用代词
No, no. You're not using any pronouns.
你一直在说 "哈特利典狱长"
You keep saying, "Warden Hartley."
我这么叫哈特利典狱长
I call Warden Hartley "Warden Hartley"
因为这就是哈特利典狱长的职位
because that's Warden Hartley's title.
就像史密斯参议员  或者琼斯警官
Like Senator Smith or Officer Jones
又或者卡通花栗鼠医生
or Doctor Cartoon Chipmunk.
-再见  -我的天
- Good-bye. - Oh, my God.
哈特利典狱长是个女人
Warden Hartley is a woman.
没错  哈特利典狱长或许是个女性
Yes, Warden Hartley may happen to be female.
但我是个女权主义者  向来不关心性别
But as a feminist, I don't notice gender.
怪不得你不告诉我
The reason you didn't mention
她是个女人  因为你想跟她滚床单
that she was a woman is because you want to sleep with her.
作为一个女权主义者  你简直让我震惊
As a feminist, I am appalled.
查理  你不能跟她睡
Charlie, you can't sleep with her.
总有一天  你们俩之间会出现问题
Eventually, something is gonna go wrong,
你们就会开始吵架
you guys are gonna start fighting,
然后她就会把我们整得生不如死
and she will make our lives a living hell.
别紧张  我不过是带她出去吃个晚餐
Relax. I'm just going to take her out to dinner,
用我的男性魅力征服她  让她恢复我的治疗小组
charm her pants off so she'll give me back my group.
看  你还是想在床上征服她
See, you're going to take her pants off.
我是说"用魅力征服她"
I said "Charm her pants off."
不管怎样你都吃定她了不是吗
Either way her pants are coming off.
这女人是典狱长
This woman is the warden
我们工作地方的头头
at the prison where we work.
我不会跟她睡的  我还没这么蠢
And I'm not gonna sleep with her. I'm smarter than that.
没错  你的脑袋是不蠢
Yes, you are smarter than that.
但通常做决定的是你的老二
Your penis, however, makes all the decisions
那玩意小学就一直没毕业
and that thing never made it past the fifth grade.
我知道  我名声在外
Look, I know I have a reputation.
那也是我辛苦挣来的
And I worked really hard for it.
但我能控制自己
But I can control myself.
好吧  或许你可以
Well, maybe.
毕竟你面对我时就控制住了
You have been able to control yourself around me.
没错  那还真是艰难
Yeah, that's been a herculean effort.
我很期待这次约会  诺兰
So looking forward to this date, Nolan.
谢谢你介绍蕾西给我认识  她还真是惹火
Thanks for introducing me to Lacey. She's smoking hot.
真高兴能看着你们俩出来约会
Glad I get to watch the two of you go out together.
而且我还得开车  所以不能喝酒
And the fact that I have to be sober because I'm working
更好不过了
makes it even better.
这么说  你是她朋友  对吗
So you're friends with her, right?
她最喜欢哪间酒吧
What's her favorite club?
她最喜欢的地方不是酒吧
Uh, well, it's not technically a club,
是间免费诊所
but she loves the free clinic.
我整天载她去那儿
Driven her there a lot.
不管她得的是啥  看来不太好根治
So whatever she's got, it's pretty stubborn.
诺兰  你好啊  昆恩
Hi, Nolan. Hey, Quinn.
你真美
You look amazing.
天哪  我们真是心灵相通
Oh, my God. We agree on everything.
我有东西送你
I got you something.
钻石耳环
Diamond earrings!
太棒了  你跟我想得一样有钱
Yay! You're as rich as I thought!
我是说  谢谢
I mean, thank you.
-诺兰  -抱歉  路上有松鼠
- Nolan! - Sorry, squirrel.
抱歉  还是松鼠
Sorry, another squirrel.
诺兰  你是有什么毛病
Nolan, what the hell is wrong with you?
又一只松鼠  或许一大队松鼠正在向我们袭来
Another squirrel. It might be a stampede.
如果我们分开  或许能增加生存的几率
Probably have a better chance of surviving if we all separate.
昆恩  快下车
Quinn, get out here.
请慢用  你们是在约会吗
Here you go. You guys on a date?
不  这只是场商务会议
No, no, no. This is just a business meeting.
她是我工作那监狱的头头
She runs the prison where I work.
那就好  有次我跟老板睡了
Well, that's good 'cause I slept with my boss once
后果很严重
and it got complicated.
那是个小型家族生意
It was a small family business
我老板就是我妹夫
and my boss was my brother-in-law.
可能就因为这样后果才这么严重
Which is probably why it got complicated.
她居然跟她妹夫睡了
Wow. She slept with her brother-in-law?
可能是因为她把表兄弟都睡光了吧
Yeah, I guess maybe she ran out of cousins.
查理  我就跟你直说了吧
Look, Charlie, I'm going to level with you.
我撤销你的治疗小组是因为许多人觉得
I'm cutting your therapy group because a lot of people think
这些罪犯应该接受惩罚
that convicted criminals should be punished,
而不是围圈坐在粉色的房间里
not sitting around in a little pink room
谈论他们的情感
talking about their feelings.
那我们就给房间重新刷个漆呗
So we'll paint the room a different color.
问题解决了  你要甜点吗
Problem solved. You want dessert?
查理  我做典狱长只是暂时的
Charlie, this warden thing is short term for me.
几个月后
In a couple of months,
我就会竞选州总检察长
I'm going to be running for state attorney general
我所提到的许多人都是竞选捐助人
and a lot of the people I'm talking about are campaign donors.
但是如果你现在中止集体治疗
But if you end the group now,
我之前的努力就都白费了
all my hard work flies out the window
留给你的是一群易怒的罪犯
and you're left with a bunch of angry prisoners.
你知道还有什么也完蛋了吗  其他罪犯们
You know what else flies out the window? Other prisoners.
抱歉  查理  这对我没什么好处
I'm sorry, Charlie. It'll look bad for me.
你知道什么才真正对你没好处吗
You know what's really gonna look bad for you?
当那群易怒的罪犯发起动乱
When your angry prisoners stage a massive riot
击落一架警用直升机
and shoot down a police helicopter
然后大家都会问你  为什么会这样
and everybody's asking you why you let it happen.
罪犯们究竟是
And how exactly
如何能击落一架直升机的呢
did the prisoners shoot down a helicopter?
这些家伙们用什么都能造出武器来
These guys can make weapons out of anything.
我见过有人用内衣弹弓射死了一只老鼠
I've seen an underwear slingshot kill a mouse at 50 paces.
所以我觉得击落个小直升机应该不在话下
So I don't think your little helicopter is gonna be a problem.
我真的很佩服你对工作的热情  查理
I'm really impressed by your passion, Charlie.
鉴于此我向你保证  我会考虑一下的
And based on that, I promise I'll reconsider.
好的  谢谢你
Well, thank you.
很有意思  我搭档还挺担心
You know what's funny? My partner was actually worried
-咱们今晚的谈话不顺利呢  -为什么
- that this meeting might not go well. - Why?
我猜想  她那么觉得是因为
I guess she figured 'cause
你是个女的  我又控制不了自己
you're a woman and I couldn't control myself.
我会勾引了你  然后又把你睡了
I'd hit on you and we'd end up sleeping together.
太埋汰我了吧
That's kind of insulting to me.
就好像我没有发言权一样
As if I wouldn't have any say in the matter.
就是啊
I know, right? I mean,
就算我觉得你超有魅力
even though I find you incredibly attractive,
也不意味着  我非得像动物一样占有你
it's not like I'm some animal that just has to have you.
就算我们有那种感觉
I mean, just because we feel that way,
也不意味着我们真的会做
doesn't mean we have to act on it.
我觉得挺生气的
I am really offended.
我也是
So am I.
她太烦人了
The nerve of her.
明天我就和乔丹说  让她别多管闲事
I'm telling Jordan tomorrow to mind her own business.
她为什么会谈论我呢
Why would she talk about me?
她根本不认得我
She doesn't even know me.
我和你说  她得和咱们两人道歉
I think she owes us both an apology, I'll tell you that.
-没错  -就是
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-你屁股打得不错  -多谢夸奖
- You're a good spanker. - Thanks.
这是我逛得最爽的一天
This is the best day of shopping ever.
所有东西都免单的感觉太棒了
It's so cool when everything's free.
不是免单的  蕾西  是我花的钱
Well, it wasn't free, Lacey. I paid for it.
我知道  但是没花我的钱
Oh, I know, but it was free for me.
神啊  你太可爱了
God, you're wonderful.
要不然你去我那里
Why don't you come over
我会扒了你那件新睡衣的
and I'll tear that new lingerie off of you?
诺兰  回我家
Nolan, take us back to my place.
不行  我做不到
No. I won't do it.
什么
What?
威廉姆斯先生  你认为你可以来这里
Mr. Williams, you think you can come in here
给蕾西买这些漂亮衣服
and buy Lacey all this fancy stuff
让她高兴得飞上了天
and make her happier than I've ever seen her?
在我眼皮子底下不可能
Not on my watch.
去找别的司机吧
Get another driver.
听着  诺兰  我明白了
Look, Nolan, I get it.
你不开心因为你喜欢蕾西  她这么招人爱
You're upset because you like Lacey and how could you not?
是啊  看看姐
I know, right? I mean, look at me.
但是你不可能追到她的
But there is no way you're ever going to get her.
她可不想找个穷酸邋遢的小伙子
She doesn't want some poor
不能给她买那些奢侈昂贵的商品
slob who can't afford to buy her expensive things.
她和你不是一类人
She's way out of your league.
她这样的女孩是要跟我这样的人在一起的
Girls like this are for guys like me.
天啊  你真是个混蛋
God, you are a dick.
给我下车
Get out.
不  不是说你  诺兰
No, not you, Nolan.
你不能和我朋友那样讲话
You can't talk to my friend that way.
这辈子再也不想见到你了  再见
I never want to see you again. Good-bye.
-但这是我租的车  -我说了再见
- But this is my limo. - I said good-bye!
拿上你的...  得了你走吧
And take your-- you know what? Just go.
真没想到你能这么做
I can't believe you did that.
我跟你有戏了
So I do have a chance with you?
没有  不可能
Oh, no. Not at all.
他说的没错  我不是你的类型
He was absolutely right. I'm totally out of your league,
但他也不能这么赤裸裸地讲出来
but you can't say stuff like that out loud.
多让穷人难过啊
It makes poor people sad.
那你可瞧好了  我现在有工作了
Well, you better watch out, 'cause now I've got a job.
有了工作  钱就来了
And once you get a job, you get money.
有了票子...
And once you get the money...
我还是送你回家吧
I'll just take you home.
你好  你卡车后面有行号码
Hi. You had a number on the back of your truck
写着我有意见就打电话
that said I should call if I had a comment.
我想说你的车技棒极了
Your driving was excellent.
不客气
You're very welcome.
搞什么飞机
Are you serious?
这叫正能量激励  白痴
It's called positive reinforcement, jackass.
换个说法
Let me try it.
作为一个闲的蛋疼的波莉安娜
As a time-wasting Pollyanna,
小说《波莉安娜》主人公  为人积极乐观
你是顶级的
you're the best.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
和新典狱长谈的怎么样了
So how'd it go with the new warden?
小组保住了  我很有说服力
My group lives on. I was incredibly persuasive
搞定这事根本不用睡她
and I didn't even have to sleep with her to get what I wanted.
抱歉  小看你了
Sorry. I underestimated you.
你的确小看我了
Yes, you did.
事成之后我才睡了她
I slept with her after I got what I wanted.
查理  你知道接下来会怎样  对不对
Charlie, you know what's going to happen now, don't you?
对  对  对  整个下午
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're going to say the same thing
你又要翻来覆去说个没完
in different ways all afternoon.
但晚上我还是会睡她
And tonight, I'm gonna to sleep with her again.
你好  谷德森先生
Hello, Mr. Goodson.
下午好  哈特利典狱长
Good afternoon, Warden Hartley.
你们俩认识吗
Have you two met?
典狱长  这是乔丹  乔丹  这是典狱长
Warden, this is Jordan. Jordan, Warden.
典狱长  乔丹
Warden, Jordan.
很高兴认识你  有空我们应该喝杯咖啡
Nice to meet you. We should get coffee sometime
你该知道虽然我是查理的合伙人
and talk about how even though Charlie and I are partners,
没有他我一样也能把诊所搞得有声有色
I can easily run the clinic without him.
你要体谅乔丹
You'll have to excuse Jordan.
她对这个世界充满了恶意
She's mad at the world.
她最爱的《动物星球》节目被取消了
They cancelled her favorite show on Animal Planet
世界上唯一以动物为主角的电视频道
而她的社交生活九成都在聊天室里
and that chat room was 90% of her social life.
上次是你请我吃饭
Hey, since you took me out last time,
我过来想看看
I just came by to see if
今晚你愿不愿意让我做饭给你吃
you wanted me to make you dinner tonight.
棒极了  我要带点什么吗
That's great. Can I bring anything?
甜点
Dessert?
或者再来场云雨
Or just the thunder again?
都要
Bring both.
没问题
Okay.
等着我的巫山云雨
I'll bring the thunder.
还有巧克力奶油派
And a chocolate cream pie.
作为你放过我们小组的小小谢礼
I mean, it's the least I can do after you spared my prison group.
这个我们得谈谈
We should talk about that.
查理  对不起  我得撤了你的小组
Look, Charlie, I'm sorry, but I have to cancel the group.
-什么  -我和顾问谈了谈
- What?! - I talked to my advisors
他们觉得从公关的角度出发
and they just felt from a PR standpoint,
那对我的形象没有益处
that it wouldn't be good for me.
那昨晚有事怎么回事
But what about last night?
我们谈了那么多
After everything we said.
也喊了那么多
And screamed.
等等  你觉得我们俩上床之后
So wait, you think that sleeping with me
你就能控制我按你说的做
guarantees that I'll do whatever you want?
我没觉得能控制你
I didn't think it would guarantee it,
但觉得你能听我的话
but I certainly thought it would help.
你居然觉得我欠你什么实在让我很恼火
The fact that you think I owe you something really pisses me off.
你感觉愤怒的话应该到我的小组来转转
Well, if you're feeling angry, you should stop by my group.
差点忘了  你把我的小组撤了
Oh, that's right. You cancelled my group.
我没时间跟你纠结个没完
You know what? I don't have time for this.
是吗  可我每天时间多的是
Really? 'Cause I've got an extra hour every day
就因为你撤了我的组
because you cancelled my group.
你又干了什么好事
What did you do?
她撤了监狱治疗组
She shut down my prison group.
我就知道你一旦睡了她
I knew if you slept with her,
你们的关系就会变得紧张又奇怪
there will be tension and weirdness.
我睡没睡她和这没有半毛钱关系
The fact that I slep with her has nothing to do with
我跟她的关系本来就够紧张奇怪的
this tention and weirdness wherever I go.
现在诊所也要关门大吉了
Now they're gonna shut down the clinic, too.
淡定点行吗  我会有办法的
Will you calm down? I'll figure this out.
你和她纠缠不清
You got involved with her.
然后又和她大吵一架
And then you got in a fight.
用不了多久
And now it's just a matter of time before
事情就会糟得连狗屎都不如
everyt completely in a crapper.
我就知道我是对的
I was right. I knew I was right.
那真是恭喜了
Well, congratulations.
真希望你屁股上也有个号码
I wish there's a number on your ass
这样我就能打给所有人
that I can call and tell everyone
告诉他们你干得棒极了
what a great job you're doing.